{
    "id": "91b7d8448fd4403791fa9edebca1f0b1",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He supported his friendâ€™s claim.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "backed off",
                "backed up",
                "backed down"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The police could not produce any evidence that would substantiate the charge of murder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bear out",
                "bear down",
                "bear up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to sell my old car and buy a new one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dispose of",
                "dispose off",
                "dispose with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "During her prolonged battle with illness she often desired death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "longed for",
                "longed on",
                "longed with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Athletes from our district won many medals at the national sports meet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bore away",
                "bore down",
                "bore up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The leader has been able to crush all opposition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bear up",
                "bear out",
                "bear down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He stopped suddenly in the middle of his story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "broke down",
                "broke off",
                "broke up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His folly has caused his ruin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "brought up",
                "brought out",
                "brought about"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He found great difficulty in converting her to his views.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bringing her out",
                "bringing her round",
                "bringing her up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His passion deprived him of his self-control.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carried him on",
                "carried him out",
                "carried him away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}